

## CONTACT

**Brazil**Rio de Janeiro

WhatsApp +55 (21) 99849-7373

🖆 Email

lukas-domingos1@hotmail.com

Portfolio
<a href="https://portfolio.mosalito.com/">https://portfolio.mosalito.com/</a>
<a href="https://github.com/lukas-loto">https://github.com/lukas-loto</a>

# **FORMATION**

2021 - Atual **UFRJ** 

2018 - 2021 CEFET/RJ Programação

### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese (mother tongue)

English (advanced)

Spanish (Basic)

#### INTEREST

WordPress Developer

Frontend Developer

PHP Developer

# **Lukas Domingos**

Full Stack Developer

#### **PROFILE**

Full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience specializing in WordPress. I am a dedicated professional, hardworking, loyal, and willing to learn and teach, striving for excellence and good results. I've always given my best for all the companies I've been through, without measuring efforts. The leaders I worked with always praised my dedication, expertise, and commitment to carry out the tasks I was delegated to.

Along my journey, I was able to learn how important Resilience, Love for the process, Owner's Vision, and Focus on the Customer are.

My skills are: TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript framework works, WordPress, PHP framework works, React, and Node. But I already had contact with other languages like Python, Java, C#, and C++.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

April 2022 - Current Full Stack Web Developer, Virginia, United States

- Developed the new Webera website on WordPress
- I Developed the frontend of the Greenmainframe website in React/TypeScript
- I developed the Greenmainframe blog in WordPress
- Developed the Beer with the Boss website
- Developed the Mototalk website
- Vector design in Adobe Illustrator
- Image design in Canva and Photoshop
- · Versioning on GitHub and GitLab
- Production of modern landing pages
- Code and/or Zapier API integrations
- Creation of animations in After Effects for the frontend
- Use of Webhooks
- Use of microservices and microfrontends
- UI/UX application
- Agile Methodology

April 2020 - April 2021 Full Stack Web Developer, Robo da Loto, Brazil

- Reproduction of Figma layouts with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery
- Use of Trello for Agile Methodology
- Versioning on GitHub
- Development in PHP/Codeigniter 4

April 2019 - April 2020 Full Stack Web Developer, Freelance

- Creation of e-commerce, blog with Frontend Publishing, landing page, and websites in general.
- Rest API, Node, React, Javascript, PHP/Codeigniter 4, Json, C, C#, C++, Python, Java, HTML, and CSS.
- Automation and notification of messages from leads by robots via WhatsApp with its own server using Baileys API

April 2019 - April 2020 Full Stack Web Developer, Internship

• API development for 1 year in Node.js and Python to generate the Federal College and College electronic time attendance sheet.